Guide to the Joseph Fellows papers, [ca. 1750-1900]
Fellows, Joseph papers, [ca. 1750-1900]
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Joseph Fellows papers, [ca.1750-1900]
4154
Joseph. Fellows
37.5 cubic ft.
Legal documents, correspondence, receipts, account books, maps.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes land and legal documents, correspondence, receipts, account books, and maps.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Land agent for Pulteney Land Office.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes land and legal documents, correspondence, receipts, account books, and maps.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Fellows, Joseph.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Link to a finding aid with a lengthy description of the collection.
- Ledger Book of Joseph Fellows (mostly personal accounts), 1822-1823; 1841 (Box 1, Volume 1)
- Account of J. Fellows with Bank of Monroe, 1830-1834 (Box 1, Volume 2)
- Small book of handwritten poetry (in envelope) (Box 1, Volume 3)
- Account of J. Fellows with Bank of Geneva, 1851-1857 (Box 1, Volume 4)
- Account of J. Fellows with N.B. Kidder, Banker, 1853-1854 (Box 1, Volume 5)
- Account of J. Fellows Co. with The Rochester City Bank, 1855-1859 (Box 1, Volume 6)
- Account of J. Fellows with Steuben County Bank, 1856-1861 (Box 1, Volume 7)
- Manuscript copy of promissory-note book, 1822-1824 (Box 1, Volume 8)
- Printed form-book of promisory notes, 1860 (Box 1, Volume 9)
- Check book (only stubs) of John Heermans, 1878-1879 (Box 1, Volume 10)
- Book with lists of "lots" and "Agencies", 1833-1837 (Box 1, Volume 11)
- J. (or S.) H. Brown's report of lands in the Buffalo and Tonawanda reservations (Box 1, Volume 12)
- Accounts of Ontario Glass Mfg. Co. with various people, 1831-1832 (Box 2, Volume 1)
- Ledger book, 1851-1852 (Box 2, Volume 2)
- Land survey of Township #10, 1849 (Box 2, Volume 3)
- 1 p. "Dr. Joseph Fellows Postage", 1830 (Box 2, Volume 3)
- Account book of J. Fellows, 1830-1836 (Box 2, Volume 4)
- Book of household accounts, 1824-1825 (Box 2, Volume 5)
- J. Fellows in Account with J.N. Hungerford's Bank (blank) (Box 2, Volume 6)
- J. Fellows - sm. bk. of accounts, 1832-1837 (Box 2, Volume 7)
- J. Fellows - scct. with Bank of the Interior (Albany), 1860-1861 (Box 2, Volume 8)
- Account of J. Fellows with N.B. Kidder, 1851-1852 (Box 2, Volume 9)
- Account of Ward and Co. with J. Fellows, Esq., 1848-1851 (Box 2, Volume 10)
- Sm. book with notes pertaining to Indian Reservations (Box 2, Volume 11)
- Q.W. Wellington and Co.'s Bank in account with H.C. Heermans, 1887-1888 (Box 2, Volume 12)
- Gillespie Surveys (Box 2, Volume 13)
- "Pass Book," J.F. Hill, Bath, 1859-1862 (Box 2, Volume 14)
- Account, of John Ward and Co. with J. Fellows, 1831-1841 (Box 2, Volume 15)
- "Banks" (accounts), 1820-1824 (Box 2, Volume 16)
- John Aird Insurance Co. (account), 1822-1832 (Box 2, Volume 17)
- J. Fellows - Oaths, 1812; Will, accounts, 1813; Ledgers, 1843-1844, 1812-1844 (Box 2, Volume 18)
- Postage accounts; "Memorandums;" various other accounts and notes, 1830-1841 (Box 2, Volume 19)
- Form book of contracts, with ms. letter drafts, 1859-1860 (Box 3, Volume 1)
- Appraisals of improvements on reservations (by Thomas Sove and Ira Cook), 1843 (Box 3, Volume 2)
- Lists of Townships (Box 3, Volume 3)
- Form book of contracts (v. much used) and other legal papers, 148-1853 (Box 3, Volume 4)
- Financial notations, 1820-1853 (Box 3, Volume 5)
- J. Fellows, "Memorandums" (Box 3, Volume 6)
- Journal and ledger, 3" legal, 1855-1867 (Box 4, Volume 1)
- Copies of letters, receipts, etc., written on back for Sodus Canal Co. Stock Receipts, 1859-1863 (Box 4, Volume 2)
- Unidentified list (Box 4, Volume 3)
- Accounts of J. Fellows Co., 1830-1851 (Box 5, Volume 1)
- "Indian Conservation Collections", 1828-1830 (Box 5, Volume 2)
- Supreme Court cases about land transactions, 1818-1825 (Box 5, Volume 3)
- Ledger, 1826-1827 (Box 5, Volume 4)
- J. Fellows ledgerbook, 1814-1834 (Box 5, Volume 5)
- Accounts, paid and received, 1831-1832 (Box 5, Volume 6)
- Accounts, paid and received, 1832 (Box 5, Volume 7)
- Account book, 1838-1839 (Box 5, Volume 8)
- Account book, 1824-1825 (Box 5, Volume 9)
- Account books, 1829-1839 (Box 6, Volume 1)
- Account for auction and balance sheet for Indian reservation, 1859 (Box 6, Volume 2)
- Accounts with Manhattan Co., Geneva Bank, Mohawk Bank, etc., 1824-1826 (Box 6, Volume 3)
- Lists of rents, receipts for land, 1852 (Box 6, Volume 4)
- Indian reservation receipt book, 1846-1847 (Box 6, Volume 5)
- Personal (household) and buisness accounts, 1818-1829 (Box 6, Volume 6)
- Buisness accounts and some household accounts, 1853-1870 (Box 6, Volume 7)
- Accounts of C. Williamson, Indian reservations, D. Caeron, etc., 1827-1831 (Box 6, Volume 8)
- "Accounts Current, Steuben Agency", 1841 (Box 7, Volume 1)
- "Accounts Current, Steuben Agency", 1845 (Box 7, Volume 2)
- "Accounts Current, Steuben Agency", 1847 (Box 7, Volume 3)
- Ledger of land transactions, 1859-1866 (Box 7, Volume 4)
- J. Fellows, ledgers, 1828-1833 (Box 7, Volume 5)
- Accounts and ledgers, 1832-1839 (Box 7, Volume 6)
- Account book, 1842-1847 (Box 8, Volume 1)
- Various contracts and agreements (forms?) (Box 8, Volume 2)
- Journal and Ledger relating to Indian reservations, 1821-1828 (Box 8, Volume 3)
- Account book - Geneva Sales (Book 22), 1818 (Box 9, Volume 1)
- J. Fellows account book, 1857-1867 (Box 9, Volume 2)
- Land purchased for taxes record book, 1834 (Box 9, Volume 3)
- Ledger, 1854-1868 (Box 9, Volume 4)
- Indexed book of legal precedents (mortgages) (Box 10, Volume 1)
- Contract book, 1845-1862 (Box 10, Volume 2)
- Check book (stubs), 1852 (Box 11, Volume 1)
- Supreme Court proceedings (Book 4), 1801-1827 (Box 11, Volume 2)
- Western lands belonging to J. Fellows (Book 5), 1838-1839 (Box 11, Volume 3)
- Accounts receivable book (Book 25), 1838-1839; 1842-1852 (Box 11, Volume 4)
- Tiisue copy book (letters), 1813-1814 (Box 11, Volume 5)
- List of lots (Box 11, Volume 6)
- Letter drafts and accounts, 1829-1831 (Box 11, Volume 7)
- Mutli-use book (cash book, scrapbook re railroads, plank road laws) (Book 29), 1813-c. 1855 (Box 12, Volume 1)
- N. and C. Low day book (in account with McCay) (Book 34), 1828-1851 (Box 12, Volume 2)
- Supreme Court brief, c. 1849 (Box 12, Volume 3)
- Index for Abstract Book 3 (Book 27), 1859-1862 (Box 12, Volume 4)
- Trustee account book, 1845-1856 (Box 12, Volume 5)
- Reservation journal (accounts), 1828-1839 (Box 12, Volume 6)
- Blotter, 1850 (Box 12, Volume 7)
- Reservation accounts (J. Fellows), 1845-1846 (Box 12, Volume 8)
- Reservation accounts, 1824 (Box 12, Volume 9)
- Accounts of T.L. Ogden, 1841 (Box 12, Volume 10)
- Account book, 1846 (Box 13, Volume 1)
- Bonds of mortgages, accounts, 1849-1850 (Box 13, Volume 2)
- Contracts, 1856 (Box 13, Volume 3)
- Reservation accounts (interest), 1845 (Box 13, Volume 4)
- Interest accounts, 1850-1851 (Box 13, Volume 5)
- Reservation accounts (interest), 1841-1847 (Box 13, Volume 6)
- Accounts (2 items), 1845 (Box 13, Volume 7)
- Accounts, 1835-1836 (Box 13, Volume 8)
- Interest accounts, 1825-1832 (Box 13, Volume 9)
- Letter book, 1832 (Box 13, Volume 10)
- Deed transactions (Box 14, Volume 1)
- Contracts, 1858-1859 (Box 14, Volume 2)
- Reservation ledger, 1828 (Box 14, Volume 3)
- J. Fellows Estate accounts, 1881-1883 (Box 14, Volume 4)
- Accounts paid, 1840-1841 (Box 14, Volume 5)
- Sales of Johnstone and Pulteney Estates, 1839 (Box 14, Volume 6)
- Interest accounts (2 items), 1841-1844; 1845-1848 (Box 14, Volume 7)
- "Memorandums", 1814-1816 (Box 14, Volume 8)
- Miscellaneous accounts, 1831-52 (Box 14, Volume 9)
- Accounts of Charles A. Williamson, 1825-1836 (Box 14, Volume 10)
- Accounts paid to David Selden, 1849-1861 (Box 14, Volume 11)
- List of lots and descriptions (Box 14, Volume 12)
- Accounts, 1834-1841 (Box 14, Volume 13)
- Orchard accounts, 1839-1840 (Box 15, Volume 1)
- Minutes, Haight and Troup, 1819 (Box 15, Volume 2)
- Sample cases, 1790 (Box 15, Volume 3)
- Surveyor's notes, accounts, misc., 1811 (Box 15, Volume 4)
- Draft letters and accounts, 1829-1830 (Box 15, Volume 5)
- Inventory, Geneva Church and promissory notes, 1808-1811 (Box 15, Volume 6)
- Account book, 1811-1812 (Box 15, Volume 7)
- Account book, Bank of Bath, 1858-1864 (Box 15, Volume 8)
- Small account books (10), c. 1814-1887 (Box 15, Volume 9)
- Ledger of J. Fellows (Book 1), 1846-1849 (Box 16, Volume 1)
- Scrapbook of clippings and notes (Box 16, Volume 2)
- Multi-Use book; land contracts, daybook, scrapbook (Book 31), 1836-1842 (Box 16, Volume 3)
- Ledger of land transcations (Book 12), c. 1855-1870 (Box 16, Volume 4)
- Daybook (Book 33), 1836-1853 (Box 17, Volume 1)
- Daybook (Book 32), 1850-1855 (Box 17, Volume 2)
- List of letters mailed, 1866 (Box 17, Volume 3)
- Court document (Box 18, Volume 1)
- Clerks Manual, 1862 (Box 18, Volume 2)
- Map of Michigan and Wisconsin, 1835 (Box 18, Volume 3)
- Home protection pamphlet, 1856 (Box 18, Volume 4)
- Arithmetic textbook, 1825 (Box 18, Volume 5)
- Navigation guide, 1848 (Box 18, Volume 6)
- Annual reports (Box 19, Volume 1)
- Advertisements and broadsides (Box 19, Volume 2)
- Legal forms (Box 19, Volume 3)
- Publications (Box 19, Volume 4)
- Legislative printed material (Box 19, Volume 5)
- Legislative printed material (Box 19, Volume 6)
- Letter book, 1891-1895 (Box 20)
- Parchment land grants, 1820 (Box 21)
- Land contracts, 1800-1880 (Box 22)
- Land contracts, 1860-1870's (Box 23)
- Land documents, 1756-1799 (Box 24)
- Land documents, 1800-1810 (Box 25)
- Land documents, 1811-1819 (Box 26-27)
- Land documents, 1811-1819 (Box 28)
- Land documents, 1820's (Box 29-34)
- Land documents, 1830's (Box 35-40)
- Land documents, 1840's (Box 41-46)
- Land documents, 1850's (Box 47-52)
- Certified tax sales documents, 1852-1854 (Box 53)
- Land documents, 1860's (Box 54-60)
- Land documents, 1870's (Box 61-63)
- Land documents; 1 fld., 1880's; 1907-1913 (Box 64)
- Land documents (Box 65-66)
- Legal documents, 1800-1840's (Box 67)
- Legal documents, 1850-1870's (Box 68)
- Buisness receipts, pre 1800-1820 (Box 69)
- Buisness receipts, 1830-1840's (Box 70)
- Buisness receipts, 1850'1860's (Box 71)
- Buisness receipts, 1860-1880's (Box 72)
- Correspondence, 1801-1839 (Box 73)
- Correspondence, 1840's (Box 74-5)
- Correspondence, 1850's (Box 76)
- Correspondence, 1860's (Box 77)
- Correspondence, 1860-1870's (Box 78)
- Maps and oversize personal papers (Box 79)
- Newspapers (Box 80)
- Land documents, 1795; 1800-1829 (Box 81)
- Land documents, 1830-1839 (Box 82)
- Land documents, 1840-1849 (Box 83)
- Land documents, 1849-1859 (Box 84)
- Land documents, 1850-1859 (Box 85)
- Land documents, 1860-1869 (Box 86)
- Land documents, 1860-1879 (Box 87)
- Land documents, 1870-1880 (Box 88)
- Tonnewanda Reservation, 1844 (Folder 1)
- Village of Tonnewanda, 1849 (Folder 1)
- Village of Tonnewanda Falls, 1843 (Folder 1)
- Phelps and Gorham purchase map, 1794 (Folder 2)
- Other New York State area maps, 1800's (Folder 3)
  Includes map of Onondaga purchase of 1817
- 3 Indiana maps, Undated (Folder 4)
- Milwaukee, 1852 (Folder 4)
- Berrien County, Montana, Undated (Folder 4)
- New York State area maps and chart, 1800's (Folder 5)
- Auction Sale of Indian Lands, 1853 (Folder 6)
- Partial of Buffalo Reservation, 1843 (Folder 6)
- 6 maps of Buffalo Creek Indian reservation, 1844 (Folder 6)
- Holland Land Co. or Buffalo Creek Reservation, 1827 (Folder 7)